Finding Aid for the Edgar Hill Duncan Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edgar Hill Duncan Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0124
22.94 Linear Feet
- Short Fiction in M ,A (Box 1)
- Paper for SAMLA ? (Box 1)
- Bear on Hand in WBP: Copy & Correspondence Tennyson & Dante Tennyson & Dante (Box 1)
- Replies to "'Bear on Hand' in WBP" Tennyson: A Modern Appraisal Lecture on Chaucer's Modernity Lecture on Chaucer's Medievalism Lecture on Med - MSS (Box 1)
- De secretis nature Arnoldi de Villa Nova (Box 1)
- Senior & Epístola solis (Box 1)
- Visio de dono gracie Johannis Dastini (Box 1)
- Summa perfectionis Geberi (Box 1)
- # 105 Geber's Sum (Box 1)
- [unlabeled; also empty] (Box 1)
- [rubberbanded together]: (Box 1)
  Summa de perfectionis Geberi variants
  Summa perfectionis Geberi - Text - Original
- Geber's Sum - English 1698 carbon of 24 pp (Box 1)
- Summa perfectionis Geberi variants (Box 1)
- Summa perfectionis Geberi Text carbon (Box 1)
- Summa perfectionis Geberi Variants Carbon (Box 1)
- Geber's Sum Final working draft - Variants (Box 1)
- Geber's Sum Variant readings (Box 1)
- [unlabeled] (Box 1)
- Geber's Sum: Variant readings # 105 (Box 1)
- [unlabeled] (Box 1)
- [unlabeled] (Box 1)
- Geber, Summa Working papers for my version (Box 1)
- BM Sloane 317, ff 27-45 In English # 105 17th Cen (Box 1)
- [loose papers inserted between first few files] (Box 2)
- Medieval Literature: Map of England, Gen. Tables (Box 2)
- Guthrie, Paper on Preface to Chaucer (Box 2)
- Chaucer, Supplement to Bibliography (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Manuscripts&Tale Order (Box 2)
- Medieval Art&Artifacts (Box 2)
- Chaucer Slides, list&showings (Box 2)
- Geoffrey of Vinsauf (Box 2)
- Eng 202 -- Deschamps (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Five passages, Form A (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Five passages, Form B (Box 2)
- Chaucer Facsimiles (Box 2)
- General Prologue&Augustine's Confessions (Box 2)
- Knight’s Tale, assignments (Box 2)
- Planetary House in Knight’s Tale (Box 2)
- Chaucer’s WBP 193-828 and Geoffrey of Vinsauf’s (Box 2)
- Documentum (Box 2)
- Wife of Bath’s horoscope (Box 2)
- Outline of Eisner’s A Tale of Wonder (Box 2)
- Wife of Bath, bibliography (Box 2)
- Merchant’s Tale, assignments (Box 2)
- Rhetorical Colors in the Franklin’s Tale (Box 2)
- Franklin’s Tale, assignments (Box 2)
- Pardoner’s tale assignments (Box 2)
- Nun’s Priest’s Tale assignments (Box 2)
- Mandeville’s Travels, facsimile (Box 2)
- Prioress’ Tale (Box 2)
- Sir Thopas (Box 2)
- Melibeus (Box 2)
- Nun’s Priest’s Tale (Box 2)
- Wife of Bath’s Pro.&Tale (Box 2)
- Friar’s Tale (Box 2)
- Clerk’s Tale (Box 2)
- Merchant’s Tale (Box 2)
- Squire’s Tale (Box 2)
- Franklin’s Tale (Box 2)
- Pardoner’s Tale (Box 2)
- Sec. Nun’s Tale (Box 2)
- Man of Law’s Tale (Box 2)
- T&C, facsimiles (Box 2)
- Troilus&Crideyde .[sic]. facsimiles (Box 2)
- T&C, facsimiles (Box 2)
- T&C, bibliography (Box 2)
- Legend of Good Women. Outline (Box 2)
- Manciple’s Prologue (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Book of Duchess (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Parliament of Fowls (Box 2)
- Chaucer: House of F_____ _ [handwritten; illegible] (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Legend of Good Women (Box 2)
- Chaucer: Troilus&Cressida (Box 2)
- Morte Arthure (Box 2)
- Medieval Lyric (Box 2)
- Romantic Period: Exams (Box 2)
- Romantic Period, reading lists (Box 2)
- Romantic Period, reading lists (Box 2)
- Romantic Period; reading lists (Box 2)
- Romantic Period, backgrounds (Box 2)
- Arnold (Box 2)
- Blake (Box 2)
- Browning (Box 2)
- Byron (Box 2)
- Clough (Box 2)
- Cold1eridge (Box 2)
- De Quincey (Box 2)
- Dickens (Box 2)
- Eliot (Box 2)
- George Eliot (Box 2)
- Fitzgerald (Box 2)
- Hazlitt&Lamb (Box 2)
- Keats (Box 2)
- Eng. 255 -- Meredith (Box 2)
- English 255, Meredith (Box 2)
- Meredith (Box 2)
- John S. Mill (Box 2)
- Newman (Box 2)
- Pater (Box 2)
- Pre-Raphaelites, bibliography (Box 2)
- Rossetti (Box 2)
- Rossetti (Box 2)
- Rossetti (Box 2)
- Ruskin (Box 2)
- Shelley (Box 2)
- Swinburne (Box 2)
- Tennyson: Poems to accompany reading on tapr[sic] (Box 2)
- Tennyson (Box 2)
- Wilde (Box 2)
- Wordsworth (Box 2)
- [occasionally papers inserted between files] (Box 3)
- Personal Vita (Box 3)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 3)
- Publications (Box 3)
- Vic. [? handwritten] Anthol. - Norton Tennyson (Box 3)
- Reprints sent to EHD by other scholars. (Box 3)
- Resume of Master’s Thesis (Box 3)
- Lily Peters (Box 3)
- American Philosophical Society Grant, 1953 (Box 3)
- Committee on experimental course in Technology and Human Values (Box 3)
- Vanderbilt Philosophical Club (Box 3)
- Phi Beta Kappa (Box 3)
- Vanderbilt U. Senate (Box 3)
- Archives Committee (Box 3)
- Medieval Studies Group (Box 3)
- Tracks Committee (Box 3)
- Vanderbilt Univ. Medieval Group, 1975 (Box 3)
- Literary Symposia (Box 3)
- Departmental Business (Box 3)
- Graduate English Club (Box 3)
- English Dept. activities (Box 3)
- Departmental Library (Box 3)
- News&Notes: English Department Library (Box 3)
- Graduate Committee -- English (Box 3)
- Prelims (Box 3)
- Departmental Library (Box 3)
- Finney Book Fund (Box 3)
- Caroline Ivey Fund (Box 3)
- Alumnus article, June 1971 (Box 3)
- Deaprtmental [sic] Library Correspondence (Box 3)
- Dept-al {sic] Library (Correspondence) (Box 3)
- Retirement Banquet, E. H. Duncan (Box 3)
- VUGENL material (Box 3)
- VUGENL material (Box 3)
- VUGENL material (Box 3)
- VUGENL material (Box 3)
- Speeches, [sic] (Box 3)
- Randolph-Macon, Class Manager (Box 3)
- Belmont College, Eng. 420, 1969 (Box 3)
- Second Knight (Box 3)
- Baron (Box 3)
- Belinda (Box 3)
- Arnold (Box 3)
- Browning (Box 3)
- Browning (Box 3)
- Victorian Seminar 318 B (Box 3)
- Eng. 318 B Records, etc. (Box 3)
- Arnold (Box 3)
- Carlyle (Box 3)
- Tennyson (Box 3)
- Replies to my "Tennyson: A Modern Appraisal." (Box 3)
- Tennyson (Box 3)
- English 318 A: Victorian (Box 3)
- Victorian Seminar 317 A Materials for 1st sem. (Box 3)
- 526-B (Box 3)
- 526-C (Box 3)
- 526 (Box 3)
- 526-A (Box 4)
- Replies to Articles on Chaucer (Box 4)
- "A Medieval Atomistic Ontology" (Box 4)
- Milton Encyclopaedia (Box 4)
- Short Fiction in Medieval English (Box 4)
- Articles on Dialects in Middle English (Box 4)
- Reprints of Duncan Articles (Box 4)
- Conference and Association newsletters, announcements, programs (Box 4)
- American International Open University (Box 4)
- Arkansas Poetry Society (Box 4)
- Center for Medieval and Early Rennassance [sic] Studies (Box 4)
- Early English Text Society (Box 4)
- English Institute (Box 4)
- Medieval Academy of America (Box 4)
- Medieval Institutes and Associations (Box 4)
- Reports to the Chaucer Committee MLA (Box 4)
- National Council of Teachers of English (Box 4)
- National Council of Teachers of English (Box 4)
- Notes and Seminar Reports: Medieval and Renaissance Institute, UNC, 1965 (Box 4)
- SAGE Symposium, "Chaucer the Love Poet", 1971 (Box 4)
- Sewanee Medieval Colloquium, April 1975 (Box 4)
- Southeastern Medieval Ass. [sic] (Box 4)
- South Atlantic Modern Language Association (Box 4)
- Southern Humanities Conference (Box 4)
- Southeastern Institute of Medieval and Renassance [sic] Studies (Box 4)
- SCMLA (Box 4)
- South Central MLA (Box 4)
- Studies in Short Fiction (Box 4)
- Tennessee ?Philological [sic] Association (Box 4)
- Tennessee College English Association (Box 4)
- Tennyson Society, 1966-23rd Univ. of Kentucky Foreign Language Conference (Box 4)
- W. Michigan Medieval Conference E. Kentucky Univ. NDEA institue (Box 4)
- [numerous loose papers at end of files] (Box 4)
- [loose items before files begin] (Box 5)
- Grade Books (Box 5)
- Grade Books (Box 5)
- [loose sheets] (Box 5)
- Jim Anderson (Box 5)
- James Andreas (Box 5)
- Haldun Braddy (Box 5)
- Emerson Brown (Box 5)
- Charles Cline (Box 5)
- Student File: M. Falwell (Box 5)
- Student File: Connie Fulmer (Box 5)
- Student File: Alan Gardner (Box 5)
- Student File: John Gardner (Box 5)
- Student File: Windley R. Hall (Box 5)
- Student File: E. LeRoy Lawson (Box 5)
- Student File: Paul G. Leroy (Box 5)
- Student File: Martha Nord (Box 5)
- Student File: Derek Pearsall (Box 5)
- Student File: Sid Vance (Box 5)
- Student File: Cleve Want (Box 5)
- John Hatcher, Research Project (Box 5)
- Student Files (Box 5)
- NAF GS1441 Fiscal Reports (Box 5)
- NSF Grant (Box 5)
- NUCMS Lecture Series, Oct. 1975 (Box 5)
- application for grant, 1970 (Box 5)
- Research Notes - Alchemy (Box 5)
- Writings: Alchemy and Chaucer̵s Canon̵s Yeoman̵s Tale (Box 5)
- Translating Alchemical Texts (Box 5)
- Chaucer & Alchemical Texts (Box 5)
- Book Reviews (Box 5)
- Book Reviews (Box 5)
- Chaucer as Love Poet (Box 5)
- Chaucer the Love Poet, publication (Box 5)
- Correspondence and material concerning the Chaucer Library publication. (Box 5)
- Publication of the Chaucer Library. (Box 5)
- Chaucer Research Bulletins (Box 5)
- Millers̵s [sic] Tale and Reeve̵s Tale (Box 5)
- Prologue (Box 5)
- Pynson̵s Chaucer (Box 5)
- Knight̵s Tale: articles and notes (Box 5)
- Chaucer Variorum Project (Box 5)
- Chaucer Variorum (Box 5)
- [unlabeled legal-size file atop others] (Box 6)
- Beowulf - Early English Literature (Box 6)
- Early English Literature (Box 6)
- Early English Literature (Box 6)
- Early English Literature (Box 6)
- Early English Drama (Box 6)
- Early English Drama (Box 6)
- Medieval Drama (Box 6)
- Medieval Drama (Box 6)
- Medieval Drama (Box 6)
- Early English Drama - Lecture Notes (Box 6)
- Eng. 304 (Box 6)
- The Play of Herod: Pro Musica (Box 6)
- The Herod Festivities at Padua (Box 6)
- Daniel: Pro Musica (Box 6)
- Cursor Mundi (Box 6)
- Early English Drama - Syntagma (Box 6)
- Music of Amsterdam (Box 6)
- Early English Drama - Hail Holy Queen (Box 6)
- Early English Drama -- An English Translation of Philipe de Mezieres' Account of the Representatio figurata (Box 6)
- Medieval Drama - Brockman (Box 6)
  "Toward an Aesthetic"
- Early English Drama - Student Work (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer (Box 6)
- Chaucer--Reports (Box 6)
- Chaucer--Reports (Box 6)
- Chaucer--Reports (Box 6)
- Chaucer Reports (Box 6)
- Reports-- Outlines & Bibliographies (Box 6)
- [yellow unlabeled box of photocopies or mimeos] (Box 7)
- Documentum f. 46, Paetria [?] Nova f. 98 (Box 7)
- Liber Hermetis artis alkymie # 38 Original (Box 7)
- Liber Hermetis artis alkymie # 38 Carbon (Box 7)
- Liber Hermetis artis alkymie # 38 (Box 7)
- # 38 Hermes (Box 7)
- B. M. Additional 41,486, ff. 218-222 A # 38 (Box 7)
- Hermes Trismegistus, "Incip liber ... " (Box 7)
- Hermes Trismegistus (Singer# 38 [illegible]) (Box 7)
- Hermes, Incipit liber (Box 7)
- Ff. IV.12,ff. 197-200 # 38 (Box 7)
- Liber de spirito occultate (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occultate (Box 7)
- Uthesia [?], Interrogationis (Box 7)
- Uthesia et Maria, Interrogationis (Box 7)
- Uthesia et Maria, Interrogationis (Box 7)
- Uthesia et Maria, Interrogationis (Box 7)
- Uthesia et Maria, Interrogationis (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occulatato (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occultate # 142 carbon (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occultate # 142 Variants (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occultate # 142 Variants (Box 7)
- Liber de spiritu occulatao # 142 Original (Box 7)
- [several files rubber-banded together]: (Box 7)
  Ebrardia, Summa aurea
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis. Original (Box 7)
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis Carbon (Box 7)
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis Xeroxes of Photostats (Box 7)
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis (Box 7)
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Baconis secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Secretum secretorum nature (Box 7)
- Text in process (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum nature ... (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum Secretorum (Box 7)
- B.M. Sloane 1091 (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Bacon, Secretum secretorum (Box 7)
- Allegorical alchemical figures [rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- Drawings (Box 7)
- Figures of alchemical apparatus (Box 7)
- Drawings of alchemical apparatus (Box 7)
- Figures of Alchemical Apparatus (Box 7)
- Figures of alchemical apparatus (Box 7)
- Drawings of Alchemical Apparatus. (Box 7)
- Figures of Alchemical Apparatus (Box 7)
- Illus. of alch. apparatus. in color (Box 7)
- 14th cen. alchemical drawings (Box 3)
- Illus. of alch. apparatus (Box 7)
- Bibl. de l'Arsenal Pictures of men&apparatus (Box 7)
- Planetae et Metalla (Box 7)
- Symbola alchemies (Box 7)
- [cards inserted between files] (Box 7)
- Table of alchemical operations (Box 7)
- [more cards inserted] (Box 7)
- Venenoso draconi volatili (Box 7)
- Lac puelle in English (Box 7)
- Sloane 212 (Box 7)
- Argentum vivum et argentum solidum [rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- B.M. Sloane 1118 [rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- Vincent, Speculum Naturale [rubber-banded together] (Box 7)
- B. M. Harley 3528 (Box 7)
- Oxford. Bodl. Ashmole 1450 (Box 7)
- Zetzner, Theatrum Chemicum V (1560) (Box 7)
- Vesio Edwardi de [illegible; rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- Maurane [?] 334 A [rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- Versus de opere lapide: Est fons carbon [rubberbanded] (Box 7)
- Centimetrum [rubber-banded] (Box 7)
- Continental Libraries (Box 8)
- English Libraries (Box 8)
- Cambridge. Gonville&Caius College Lib. (Box 8)
- Cambridge. St. John's College Lib. (Box 8)
- Cambridge. Trinity Coll. Library (Box 8)
- Cambridge. University Library (Box 8)
- Glasgow. University Lib. (Box 8)
- London. Brit. Mus. Royal Collection (Box 8)
- Oxford All Souls' Coll. Lib. (Box 8)
- Oxford. Bodleian Lib. Bodly MSS (Box 8)
- Oxford. Bodleian Lib. Fairfax&E. Museo MSS (Box 8)
- Oxford. Corpus Christi Coll. Library (Box 8)
- Oxford. Bodleian Lib. Ashmole MSS (Box 8)
- Oxford. Bodleian Lib. Digby MSS (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [unlabeled] (Box 8)
- [in box: 2 unlabeled files; 1 labeled Geb Sum] (Box 8)
- Dastin’s Epistola (Box 9)
- John Dastin: A Letter on the Philosopher’s Stone (Box 9)
- John Dastin: A Letter on the Philosopher’s Stone (Box 9)
- John Dastin: A Letter on the Philosopher’s Stone (Box 9)
- [package of photos between files] (Box 3)
- Dastin’s Vision (Box 9)
- The Vision of the Gift of Grace (Box 9)
- A Vision or John Dastin about The Gift of Grace (Box 9)
- The Vision of John Dastin about The Gift of Grace (Box 9)
- Vision of John Dastin (Box 9)
- Bull Forbidding The Practice of Alchemy [manila folder] (Box 9)
- Pope John XXII: Spondent Quas (Box 9)
- Geber’s Sum (Box 9)
- No. 8 The Little Golden Book (Box 9)
- # 10 Senior Zadith (Box 9)
- Speculum (Box 9)
- Dastin’s Libellus Aureus # 8 (Box 9)
- No. 8 The Little Golden Book (Box 9)
- Dastin’s Libellus aureus # 7 (Box 9)
- A Letter of John Dastin about the Philosopher’s Stone (Box 9)
- # 64 Alexander (Box 3)
- Alexander Rex Persarum [?], Epistola (Box 9)
- Brussels, Rib. [?] Ray. (Box 9)
- Printed Book Avriferae Artis (Box 9)
- Printed text in Incipit Geber (Box 9)
- [unlabeled] (Box 9)
- The Mirror of Philosophy (Box 9)
- Spec Phil (Box 9)
- The Green Lion (Box 9)
- Roger Bacon&Bro. Raymond (Box 9)
- The Green Lion (Box 9)
- The Green Lion # 5 (Box 9)
- addendum to # 5 transcription&tr. into Mod. Eng. (Box 9)
- Verbum Abbre de Leone Viride (Box 9)
- Bacon’s Speculum (Box 9)
- Final Original # 4 Bacon Speculum (Box 9)
- Bacon’s Speculum # 4 (Box 9)
- Bacon’s Mirror of Sec. of Alch. (Box 9)
- Reymundus Verbum abreviatum # 5 (Box 9)
- [unlabeled] (Box 9)
- Brother Raymond The Green Lion (Box 9)
- [papers inserted between files] (Box 9)
- Wm. Salmon’s Eng. version of # 105 (Box 9)
- Paris - Bibl. Nat. Fonds Lat. (Box 9)
- Geber, Summa (Box 9)
- Geber, Summa (Box 9)
- Manget # 105 opening # ofd 4 books (Box 9)
- Geber, Summa (Box 9)
- Arnald De secretis naturae (Box 9)
- [bound portfolio] Latin Alchemy of the Fourteenth Century
- B.M. Sloane, 1091 (Box 9)
- St. Gallen Stadtsbibl. Vadiana (Box 9)
- Geber, Summa (Box 9)
- Geber, Summa (Box 9)
- Printed Text Geber, 1475 (Box 9)
- [manila envelope w/ note re Geber's Summa ] (Box 10)
- Summa perfectionis Geber (Box 10)
- France -- Corbett I&II (Box 10)
- Brussels, Bibliotheque Royale de Belgique (Box 10)
- Bernkastel-Kues, St. Nicholas-Hospital (Box 10)
- Munich, Bayerische Staats-Bibliothek (Box 10)
- Vienna. National-Bibliothek (Box 10)
- Venice. Biblioteca Nazionale di San Marco (Box 10)
- St. Gallen. stadt [?] Bibliothaca Vadiana (Box 10)
- France. Paris. Bibl. de l'Arsenal, Martin (Box 10)
- Bologna. Biblioteca Universitaria di (Box 10)
- Palermo, Biblioteca Communale (Box 10)
- U. of Penn. Lib. E.F. Smith Coll. (Box 10)
- Yale Univ. Lib. Mellon Coll. (Box 10)
- Index is of my Alchimical Photostats and Films (Box 10)
- Correspondence re Alchemy projects with Library Scholars (Box 10)
- Medieval Text Association (Box 10)
- [unlabeled: books&notes] (Box 10)
- Photostats&Films according to location (Box 10)
- Medieval Alchemical Texts: Prospectus (Box 10)
- Table of Contents of Alchemical Anthologies (Box 10)
- Cat. of Incipitis (Box 10)
- [book] Handbook for Contributors to the Chaucer Library
- Reti, "Historia del Atanor" (Box 10)
- Handwriting in MSS (Box 10)
- Publishing by Photo-copying (Box 10)
- Alchemy (Box 10)
- [unlabeled] (Box 10)
- [label torn off] (Box 10)
- Alchemy: Notes - Milton mainly (Box 10)
- Alchemy in Milton (Box 10)
- The Nat. Hist. of Metals&Minerals in Universe of PL (Box 10)
- Article on Milton. Osiris (Box 10)
- Chaucer&Milton (Box 10)
- Fludd, Robert (Box 10)
- Swar, John Speculum Mundi (Box 10)
- The Canon's Yeoman's Tale (Box 10)
- Chaucer - [illegible] art on CYT (Box 10)
- The Lit. of Alch.&CYT Xerox (Box 10)
- The Lit. of Alch.&CYT Xerox (Box 10)
- Chaucer's CYT&the Lit. of Alch. (First version) (Box 10)
- The Literature of Alchemy&Chaucer's CYT (Box 10)
- Articles on CYT --- (Box 10)
- Lodge and Agrippa (Box 10)
- Lodge&Agrippa. V.S. in Hum (Box 10)
- Donne (Box 10)
- Ben Jonson (Box 10)
- Vaughan, Henry (Box 10)
- MSS of Med. Poetics (Box 10)
- Documentum of Geoff. of Vinsauf (Box 10)
- Medieval Rhetoric (Box 10)
- Narrative Short Fiction in MA (Box 10)
- Mid Eng. Short .Fiction (Box 10)
- Short Fiction in MA (Box 10)
- # 229 Text&VR (Box 11)
- Arnaldi de Villa Nova De secretis nature (Box 11)
- De secretis nature de Arnaldi de Villa Nova carbon (Box 11)
- De secretis nature de Arnaldi de Villa Nova original (Box 11)
- Arnald De Secretis Nature (Box 11)
- De secretis nature Arnaldi de Villa Nova (Box 11)
- # 229 (Box 11)
- De secretis nature Arnaldi de Villa Nova (Box 11)
- Arnald de Sec. Nat. (Box 11)
- Arnald, De Secretis Nature (Box 11)
- Arnald - De Secretis Nature (Box 11)
- Arnald, De Secretis Naturae (Box 11)
- Arnald de Secretis Naturae (Box 11)
- Arnald, De Secretis Nature (Box 11)
- Arnald, De Secretis Nature Bacon, Spec. Alchemiae (Box 11)
- Arnaid, De Secretis Nature (Box 11)
- Arnald, de Sec. Nat. (Box 11)
- Arnald, de Sec. Nat. (Box 11)
- Oxford. Bodl. E. Musio 63 (Box 11)
- Arnald, Opera naperimme [?] revisa (Box 11)
- Ulstadt, Ceolum Philosophorurn (Box 11)
- Arnald, De Lapide Philosophorum (Box 11)
- Speculum secretorum alchernie Rogeri Baconis (Box 11)
  [several files rubber-banded together]
- Baconis de Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Bacon De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Verbum abbreviatum fratris Reymundi de viridi leone (Box 11)
- De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Verbum abbreviatum fratris .... (Box 11)
- Verbum abbreviatum fratris .... (Box 11)
- Verbum abbreviatum fratris .... (Box 11)
- Secretum secretorum nature Rogeri Baconis and Verbum abbreviatum fratris .... (Box 11)
- Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Oxford. Bodl. Ashmole, 1450 (Box 11)
- ? [sic] Fragment of Bacon, De Leone Viridi (Box 11)
- Paris. Bibl. de l'Arsenal (Box 11)
- Sanioris Medicinae R. Bacon (Box 11)
- Arnald's Rosarium (Box 11)
- Arnaldi de Villa Nova Rosarius (Box 11)
- Working Text - Arnald's Rosarius (Box 11)
- Rosarius Arnaldi de Villa Nova Text Original (Box 11)
- Rosarius Arnaldi de Villa Nova Variants original (Box 11)
- Rosary Translation (Box 11)
- Rosary. Variants (Box 11)
- Rosary -- notes (Box 11)
- Arnald's Rose-Garland (Box 11)
- Arnald's Rosary (Box 11)
- Paris. Bib. de l'Arsenal, 2872 (Box 11)
- Arnald, Rosarius (Box 11)
- Cambridge. Corpus Christi 99 (Box 11)
- Bern-Kastel Kues Arnald's Rosarius (Box 11)
- Rerum natura omnia .... (Box 11)
- Arnald, Rosarius (Box 11)
- Arnald Rosarium (Box 11)
- Arnald, Rosarium (Box 11)
- Rerum natura liquabilia sunt .... (Box 11)
- [loose pages] (Box 12)
- [files rubber-banded together] (Box 12)
- Bull of Pope John XXII: Spondent guas variants (Box 12)
- Bull of Pope John XXII: Spondent guas carbon (Box 12)
- Bull of Pope John XXII: Spondent guas ... original (Box 12)
- Bull of Pope John XXII: Spondent quas ... variants (Box 12)
- Decree of Pope John XXII: Spondent quas ... (Box 12)
- Speculum Phil (Box 12)
- Speculum philosophie magistri Johannis carbon (Box 12)
- Speculum philosophie magistri Johannis Dastini [?] (Box 12)
- Speculum philosophie magistri Johannis Dastini (Box 12)
- Dastin, Speculum Philosophie (Box 12)
- Dastin, Speculum Philosophie (Box 12)
- Libellus aureus Johannis Dastini Original (Box 12)
- Visio de dono gracie Johannis dastini variants (Box 12)
- Rosarius transcript variants&partial trans. (Box 12)
- Rosary -- pencil copy (Box 12)
- Rerum natura omnium liquefacibilum (Box 12)
- Rerum natura omnia liquabilia sunt (Box 12)
- Rerum natura omnia liquabilia sunt naturaliter ex (Box 12)
- Arnald, Opera Omnia (Box 12)
- Arnald, Opera (Box 12)
- Arnald, Rosarium (Box 12)
- Thomas text of Icocedrom [files rubber-banded] (Box 12)
- Oxford. Bodl. Ashmole 1452 [rubber-banded] (Box 12)
- Camb. Univ. Lib. 220 (Box 12)
- Camb. Trinity Coll. 916 (Box 12)
- Camb. Univ. Lib. (Box 12)
- Zetzner, Thiatrum Chimicum (Box 12)
- Carob. St. John’s Coll. (Box 12)
- Oxford. Bodl. E Musio 63 (Box 12)
- # 817 B.M. Harley 2407 (Box 12)
- Arnald, Opera Omnia [rubber-banded] (Box 12)
- [following books, periodicals, & reprints piled atop ordered files]: (Box 13)
- Die funktionen des erzahlers in chaucers... (Box 13)
- Chaucer and the French Poet Graunson (Box 13)
- Shakespeare’s Comment on Mediaeval Romance... (Box 13)
- The Two Petros in the “Monkes Tale” (Box 13)
- Joan of Kent and the Order of the Garter (Box 13)
- Astronomical Lore in Chaucer (Box 13)
- Modern Language Review vol XLIV no 2, April 1949 (Box 13)
- [following file atop others]: (Box 13)
- Venice. Bibl. Marciana (Box 13)
- [reproduction of map in manila envelope] (Box 13)
- [following books, periodicals & reprints in order]: (Box 13)
- Romania Revue Trimestrielle, 1974 2-3 (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s Ancient and Biblical World (Box 13)
- Dramatic Irony in Chaucer (Box 13)
- Saint Jerome in Jankyn’s Book of Wikken Wyves (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s Official Life (Box 13)
- Chaucer and the Seven Deadly Sins (Box 13)
- Jankyn’s Book of Wikken Wyves: Medieval.... (Box 13)
- Theodulus: A Medieval Textbook (Box 13)
- A New Interpretation of The Parlement of Foules (Box 13)
- Medieval Rhetoric in the Book of the Duchesse (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s Legend of Medea (Box 13)
- The Dry Sea and the Carrenare (Box 13)
- A Note on Chaucer’s Attitude Toward Love (Box 13)
- On the Date of Chaucer’s Astrolabe (Box 13)
- A Love Epistle by ’Chaucer’ (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s “Colle Tregetour” (Box 13)
- A Possible Source for Chaucer’s Hous of Fame (Box 13)
- Echoes of the Anathema in Chaucer (Box 13)
- Chaucer and an Italian Translation of the Heroides (Box 13)
- Jean de Meun et Chaucer, Traduceurs... (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s Version of the Aeneid (Box 13)
- Chaucer’s Eagles and Their Choice, February 14 (Box 13)